Contact Information

Email

fede.lopez89@gmail.com

Address

Lomas de Zamora, Buenos Aires, Argentine.

Phone

(+54911) 5501-9617

Date of birth

03-11-1989

Nationality

Argentinian

Link

https://ar.linkedin.co m/publicprofile/in/federicogabriel-lópezb8754254?

Skills

COBOL

JCL

SQL

DB2

Linux

HTML5

CSS3

Javascript

MongoDB

Bootstrap

SASS

NodeJs

Git

ReactJs

SVN

Control-M

Languages

Spanish

Native

English

Advanced

Federico Gabriel López

Fullstack Developer | COBOL Mainframe Developer

I'm a Fullstack Web Developer and Mainframe Cobol Developer with more than ten years of experience in technology providing my services within the banking area. I carry out analysis, development and testing task until its implementation in production.

Experience

Buenos Aires, Argentina 2020 - Present

Buenos Aires, Argentina February 2015 - Present

Buenos Aires, Argentina February 2014 - January 2015

Buenos Aires, Argentina October 2012 - February 2014

Buenos Aires, Argentina March 2010 - September 2012

React Developer

ICBC

I started taking development on frontend tasks in particular on ReactJs for an internal app in the bank for the area of compliance.

Sr Mainframe COBOL Developer ICBC

Area: Anti-Money Laundering
Impact analysis. Effort's estimation and budget
developments. COBOL programming. BATCH & Online
(CICS/ALTAMIRA) using VSAM / QSAM files, MQ and
DB2. Unit, integral and user tests.

Functional Analyst COBOL

ISBAN

Area: Risk managment (systems in recovery)
Review and acceptance of requirements.
Preparation of technical designs for delivery to
a Soft Factory. Acceptance and approval of
developments made by them. Attention to
productive incidents.

■ Sr Mainframe COBOL Developer

Area: Market and Liabilities.
Functional analysis. Impact analysis.
Development of COBOL components in TSO/HOST.

COBOL Developer

Accenture

Project: IBERDROLA from Spain.

Development of COBOL components Batch&Cics. Use of DB2, MQ, JCLs. Use of CMii 3.

Education

BA, Argentina 2020 - 2021

BA, Argentina 2008 - 2015 FullStack NodeJs
Education IT

Computer systems Engineering National University of Technology Incompleted. Third year reached.

Bachelor's degree in Business Administration Institute Euskal - Echea

BA, Argentina 2004 - 2006